Trice, Harrison M. Additional Papers /4164
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Installation - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form) #1, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 60)
- Installation - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Interviewer Form) #2, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 61)
- Installation - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form) #2, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 62)
- Installation - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Interviewer Form) #3, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 63)
- Installation - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form) #3, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 64)
- Western Electric Individual Cases - Cincinnati, Cleveland, and Cockeysville (Box 22, Folder 65)
- Western Electric Individual Cases - Columbus (Box 22, Folder 66)
- Western Electric Individual Cases - Dallas, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 67)
- Western Electric Individual Cases - Dallas continued (Box 22, Folder 68)
- Dallas Works EAP (Box 22, Folder 69)
- Research on Alcoholism Program - Personnel Information Summary - Dallas Service Center and Northern Texas Installation, 1979- 1980 (Box 22, Folder 70)
- 15-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 71)
- 15-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 72)
- 15-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 73)
- 15-03-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 74)
- 16-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 75)
- 16-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 76)
- 16-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 77)
- 16-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 78)
- 16-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 79)
- 16-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 80)
- 16-02-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 81)
- 17-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- 17-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- 17-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- 17-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- 17-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- 17-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- 17-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- 17-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- 17-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- 17-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #5 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #6, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #6 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #7, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #7 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #8, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- 15-03-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #8 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- 16-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- 16-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- 16-02-1-2 - "B" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- 16-02-1-2 - "B" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- 16-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- 16-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- 17-01-2-2 - "B" Manager Interview #6, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- 17-01-2-2 - "B" Manager Interview #6 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #7, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #7 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- 17-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #8, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 47)
- 17-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #8 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- 17-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #9, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 49)
- 17-02-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #9 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 50)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #10, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 51)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #10 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 52)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #11, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 53)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #11 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 54)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #12, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 55)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #12 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 56)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #13, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 57)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #17 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 58)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #14, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 59)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #14 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 60)
- 17-01-1-2 - "B" Manager Interview #15, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 61)
- 17-01-1-2 - "B" Manager Interview #15 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 62)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #16, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 63)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #16 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 64)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #17, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 65)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #17 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 66)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #18, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 67)
- 17-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #18 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 68)
- General Manager's Experiences with Alcoholism Program (15-3-1-1 and 16-2-1-1), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 69)
- 17-01-1-1 - General Manager's Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Interviewer Form) #1, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 70)
- 17-01-1-1 - General Manager's Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form) #1, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 71)
- 17-01-1-1 - General Manager's Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Interviewer Form) #2, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 72)
- 17-01-1-1 - General Manager's Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form) #2, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 73)
- 15-03-1-1 and 16-02-1-1 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Interviewer Form), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 74)
- 15-03-1-1 and 16-02-1-1 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 75)
- 16-02-1-1 - Staff Advisors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Interviewer Form), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 76)
- 16-02-1-1 - Staff Advisors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 77)
- 17-01-1-1 - Staff Advisors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Interviewer Form), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 78)
- 17-01-1-1 - Staff Advisors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 79)
- 15-03-1-1 - Staff Advisors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Interviewer Form), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 80)
- 15-03-1-1 - Staff Advisors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 81)
- 15-03-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Interviewer Form), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 82)
- 15-03-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 83)
- 16-02-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Interviewer Form), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 84)
- 16-02-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 85)
- 17-01-3-2 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Interviewer Form) #1, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- 17-01-3-2 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form) #1, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- 17-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Interviewer Form) #2, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- 17-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form) #2, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- 17-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Interviewer Form) #3, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- 17-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form) #3, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Western Electric Individual Case Data - Denver (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Denver Composite Notes (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Denver Composite Notes continued (Box 24, Folder 9)
- EAP Interview Schedule - Palmquist, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Interview with Mr. Palmquist, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Interview with Mr. Palmquist (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  Copy of the material in folder 11
- Interview with Mr. Palmquist (Second Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  Copy of the material in both folder 11 and folder 12
- EAP Interview Schedule - V.G. Zagarella, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Interview with V.G. Zagarella, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Interview with Tom McKee, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Interview with Tom McKee (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  Copy of the material in folder 16
- Interview with Tom McKee (Second Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  Copy of the material in both folder 16 and folder 17
- EAP Interview Schedule - E.D. Hoffman, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Interview with E.D. Hoffman, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Interview with E.D. Hoffman (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  Copy of the material in folder 20
- EAP Interview Schedule - Present General Manager(Denver Regional Center), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Interview with Present General Manager, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Interview with Present General Manager (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  Copy of the material in folder 23
- EAP Interview Schedule - Head Nurse (Denver Regional Service Center), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Interview with Head Nurse, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Interview with Head Nurse (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  Copy of the material in folder 26
- Notes on Interview with Head Nurse, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Notes on Interview with Head Nurse (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Notes on Interview with Head Nurse (Second Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  Copy of the material in both folder 28 and folder 29
- EAP Interview Schedule - Dr. Zarlingo, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Interview with Dr. Zarlingo, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Interview with Dr. Zarlingo (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Interview with Dr. Zarlingo (Second Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  Copy of the material in both folder 32 and folder 33
- EAP Interview Schedule - Dr. Zarlingo Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Notes on Interview with Dr. Zarlingo, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Notes on Interview with Dr. Zarlingo (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  Copy of the material in folder 36
- Notes on Interview with Dr. Zarlingo (Second Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  Copy of the material in both folder 36 and folder 37
- EAP Interview Schedule - Male Section Chief (Denver Regional Center), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Interview with Male Section Chief, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Interview with Male Section Chief (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  Copy of the material in folder 40
- Interview with Male Section Chief (Second Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  Copy of the material in both folder 40 and folder 41
- EAP Interview Schedule - William Goldenstein, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- Interview with William Goldenstein, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Interview with William Goldenstein (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  Copy of the material in folder 44
- Interview with William Goldenstein (Second Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  Copy of the material in both folder 44 and folder 45
- EAP Interview Schedule - Janice Beyer Interview of William Goldenstein, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 47)
- Janice Beyer Interview of William Goldenstein, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 48)
- Janice Beyer Interview of William Goldenstein (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  Copy of the material in folder 48
- Janice Beyer Interview of William Goldenstein (Second Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  Copy of the material in both folder 48 and folder 49
- Janice Beyer Interview of William Goldenstein (Third Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  Copy of the material in folders 48, 49, and 50
- Interview with Larry McGinley, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 52)
- Interview with Larry McGinley (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  Copy of the material in folder 52
- Interview with Larry McGinley (Second Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  Copy of the material in both folder 52 and folder 53
- EAP Interview Schedule - Janice Beyer Interview of Larry McGinley, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 55)
- Janice Beyer Interview of Larry McGinley, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 56)
- Janice Beyer Interview of Larry McGinley (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  Copy of the material in folder 56
- Janice Beyer Interview of Larry McGinley (Second Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  Copy of the material in both folder 56 and folder 57
- EAP Interview Schedule - Jim Blystone, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 59)
- Interview with Jim Blystone, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 60)
- Interview with Jim Blystone (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  Copy of the material in folder 60
- Interview with Jim Blystone (Second Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  Copy of the material in both folder 60 and folder 61
- EAP Interview Schedule - Jon Smith, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 63)
- Interview with Jon Smith, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 64)
- Interview with Jon Smith (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  Copy of the material in folder 64
- EAP Interview Schedule - P.A.R., 1979 (Box 24, Folder 66)
- EAP Interview Schedule - Joint Interview with James Kenefick and John Edward Smith, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 67)
- Joint Interview with James Kenefick and John Edward Smith, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 68)
- Joint Interview with James Kenefick and John Edward Smith (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 69)
- Joint Interview with James Kenefick and John Edward Smith (Second Duplicate), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 70)
- Western Electric Individual Case Data - Detroit (Box 24, Folder 71)
- Background on Hawthorne Works, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 72)
- Hawthorne Notes, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 73)
- Hawthorne Case Lists (Box 24, Folder 74)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #6, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 75)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #6 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 76)
- 02-01-2-1 - "B" Manager Interview #7, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 77)
- 02-01-2-1 - "B" Manager Interview #7 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 78)
- 02-01-1-2 - "B" Manager Interview #8, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 79)
- 02-01-1-2 - "B" Manager Interview #8 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 80)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #9, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 81)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #9 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 82)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #10, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 83)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #10 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 84)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #11, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 85)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #11 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 86)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #12, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 87)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #12 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 24, Folder 88)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #13, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #13 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #14, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #14 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #15, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #15 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #16, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #16 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #17, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #17 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #18, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #18 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #19, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #19 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #20, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #20 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #21, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #21 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #22, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #22 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- 02-01-2-1 - "B" Manager Interview #23, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- 02-01-2-1 - "B" Manager Interview #23 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #24, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #24 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #25, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #25 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- 02-01-1-2 - "B" Manager Interview #26, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- 02-01-1-2 - "B" Manager Interview #26 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #27, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #27 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #28, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #28 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #29, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #29 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #30, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #30 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #31, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #31 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #32, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #32 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #33, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #33 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #34, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #34 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #35, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #35 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #36, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #36 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 48)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #37, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 49)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #37 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 50)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #38, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 51)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #38 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 52)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #39, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 53)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #39 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 54)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #40, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 55)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #40 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 56)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #41, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 57)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #41 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 58)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 59)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #1 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 60)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 61)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #2 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 62)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 63)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #3 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 64)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 65)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #4 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 66)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 67)
- 02-01-1-1 - "B" Manager Interview #5 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 68)
- 02-01-1-1 - Staff Advisors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 69)
- 02-01-1-1 - Staff Advisors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 70)
- 02-01-1-2 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #1, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 71)
- 02-01-1-2 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #1 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 72)
- 02-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 73)
- 02-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 74)
- 02-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 75)
- 02-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #3 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 76)
- 02-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #4, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 77)
- 02-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #4 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 78)
- 02-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #5, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 79)
- 02-01-1-1 - Union Officials' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #5 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 80)
- 02-01-1-1 - General Manager's Experiences with Alcoholism Program #1, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 81)
- 02-01-1-1 - General Manager's Experiences with Alcoholism Program #1 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 82)
- 02-01-1-1 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 83)
- 02-01-1-1 - Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program #2 (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 84)
- 02-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #6, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 85)
- 02-01-1-1 - "A" Manager Interview #6 (Form for Respondent), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 86)